

Android developer · Software Engineer · Data Scientis

Faculty of Computer Engineering and Science, Shahid Beheshti University, Tehran, Iran

🛘 (+98) 991-277-5711 | 🗷 kamyababedi@gmail.com | 🏕 www.kamyababedi.com | 🗗 KamyabAbedi | 🗖 KamyabAbedi

Summary_

Current I'm third year student of CE at Shahid Beheshti University and interested in Back-end programming, IT security, ML and other geek stuff. 2+ years experience specializing in the Android development, plus 1 years experience using Adobe XD. Super nerd who loves Linux and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises. I'm passionate about my work. Because I love what I do, I have a steady source of motivation that drives me to do my best

Education

Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, Shahid Beheshti University

Tehran, Irai

B.Sc. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Sep.2018 - PRESENT

- During my degree at Shahid Beheshti University I learnt lots of key skills such as team work and project management. Although we mainly focused on software development and the principles of programming I use a lot of these skills to my advantage in my day to day work.
- Received full scholarship from Shahid Beheshti University(tuition waiver).
- One of Iran's 4 top universities.
- Supervisor: Prof. Hamid Reza Mahdiani
- · Cumulative GPA: 3/4

Shahid Beheshti High School

Tehran Iran

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA IN MATH AND PHYSICS

Sep. 2014 - Sep. 2018

- Received full scholarship from Shahid Beheshti School(tuition waiver).
- · Cumulative GPA: 3.85/4

Work Experience

Jahad Daneshgahi Institute

Tehran, Iran

TEACHER• Teaching Fundamental of programing.

Determined and graded homework, computer assignments and final projects.

Shahid Beheshti University

Tehran, Iran

TEACHING ASSISTSNT, TECHNICAL WRITING AND PRESENTATION COURSE

Jan. 2021 - PRESENT

Sep. 2020 - Jan. 2021

- Held TA sessions.
- Determined and graded homework, computer assignments.
- Under the supervision of Dr. Neshati.

Shahid Beheshti University

Tehran, Iran

TEACHING ASSISTSNT, FUNDAMENTAL OF PROGRAMING COURSE

Sep. 2020 - Jan. 2021

- Managed the TA Group for this semesters and changed the TA class syllabus to teach new students Android Development.
- · Held TA sessions.
- Determined and graded homework, computer assignments and final projects.
- Under the supervision of Dr. Abdoos.

Android Developer

Iran

FREELANCE

Sep. 2019, PRESENT

• I was asked to update an existing Android app to the latest version of Android and to fix any issues caused by this as well as a few other existing issues.

Honors & Awards

Ranked within the top 1%, among 144,437 participants in the annual Iranian University Entrance Exam for Bachelor's degree.

Tehran, Iran

2017 **Ranked within the top 10 GPAs**, among the 512 Students of the Math and Physics program at Shahid Beheshti School.

Tehran, Iran

June 4, 2021 Kamyab Abedi · Résumé 1

COMPETITIVE PROGRAMMING

Ranked 53th, among 1328 contestants, Code Star, Front-end Contest in Quera website. 2021 Tehran, Iran Tehran, Iran

2020 Ranked 68th, among 874 contestants, Code Star, Programming Contest in Quera website.

Project

"Snappfood" Backend clone - Golang

PROJECT OF INTERNET ENGINEERING COURSE

Jul. 2021

- Restful APIs for Food Delivery application developed using Golang.
- Internet Engineering course, **Dr. Parham Alvani**, Shahid Beheshti University.

"Snappfood" Frontend clone - React

PROJECT OF INTERNET ENGINEERING COURSE

- A Food Delivery application built with React JS.
- Internet Engineering course, Dr. Parham Alvani, Shahid Beheshti University.

The Matson Evaluation of Social Skills - Python

PROJECT OF DATA MINING COURSE

May. 2021

- The Matson Evaluation of Social Skills with Youngsters(MESSY) and its Adaptation for Iranian children and adolescents.
- Data Mining course, **Prof. Alireza Talebpoor**, Shahid Beheshti University.

Decaf Compiler - Java

PROJECT OF COMPILER COURSE

Jan. 2021

- Implementation a compiler for decaf language. Decaf is a simple small object-oriented language similar to C/C++/Java languages.
- · Used lexer/scanner generator, LALR parser generator.
- Compiler course, Prof. Ghassem Jaberipur, Shahid Beheshti University.

"Othello" game - Python

PROJECT OF AI COURSE

- · Implementation of smart agent for Othello game.
- Used Alpha-beta pruning and Minimax algorithm.
- · Artificial Intelligence and Expert Systems course, Dr. Armin Salimi-Badr, Shahid Beheshti University.

library management system - Java

PROJECT OF DS COURSE

- Design and Implementation of Library Management System.
- Used KD-tree and Trie Data Structures
- that was an application for assisting a librarian in managing a book library in a university. The system would provide basic set of features to add/update members, add/update books, and manage check in specifications for the systems based on the client's statement of need.
- Data structure course, Dr. Ahmad Ali Abin, Shahid Beheshti University.

"Lidingeram" Messenger Application - Java

PROJECT OF AP COURSE

- · developed a messenger application for Android phones.
- · Used socket programming.
- AP course, Dr. Mojtaba Vahidi-asl, Shahid Beheshti University.

"Jetpack Joyride" game by Halfbrick Studios - C++

PROJECT OF ITP COURSE Jan. 2019

- implement Jetpack Joyride game with SDL library.
- Used SDL and SBDL library that designed to provide low level access to audio, keyboard, mouse, joystick, and graphics hardware via OpenGL and Direct3D. It is used by video playback software, emulators, and popular games including Valve's award winning catalog and many Humble Bundle games.
- ITP course, Dr. Sadegh Aliakbary, Shahid Beheshti University.

"2 Cars" game by Ketchapp - C++

MINI PROJECT OF ITP COURSE

- implement 2 cars game with SDL library.
- Used SDL and SBDL library that designed to provide low level access to audio, keyboard, mouse, joystick, and graphics hardware via OpenGL and Direct3D. It is used by video playback software, emulators, and popular games including Valve's award winning catalog and many Humble Bundle games.
- ITP course, Dr. Sadegh Aliakbary, Shahid Beheshti University.

JUNE 4, 2021 KAMYAB ABEDI · RÉSUMÉ

"Doodle jump" game by Lima Sky - C++

MINI PROJECT OF ITP COURSE Nov. 2018

- implement Doodle jump game with SDL library.
- Used SDL and SBDL library that designed to provide low level access to audio, keyboard, mouse, joystick, and graphics hardware via OpenGL and Direct3D. It is used by video playback software, emulators, and popular games including Valve's award winning catalog and many Humble Bundle games.
- ITP course, Dr. Sadegh Aliakbary, Shahid Beheshti University.



Programming Languages:

Java (Advanced), C/C++ (Advanced), Python (Intermediate), JavaScript (Intermediate), Go(Intermediate), MATLAB(Intermediate), VHDL (Intermediate), Verilog (Intermediate), Assembly(Fair).

Other Languages:

HTML/CSS (Intermediate), SQL (Fair).

Databases:

MySQL (Intermediate), MongoDB (Intermediate).

Other:

Git (Advanced).

Workshops & Courses _____

| 2020 | Structuring Machine Learning Projects Course, Prof. Andrew NG. | Coursera Website |
|------|--|------------------|
| 2020 | Developing Android Apps Course, some Android course by Google. | Udacity Website |
| 2020 | The Hands On Machine Learning Cours, Learn and understand Machine Learning from scratch. | Udemy Website |
| 2019 | Human-Centered Design, by University of California San Diego. | Coursera Website |

Languages _____

- Persian (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- German (Elementary)

Memberships_

- **Member of the Student Scientific Association,** Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, Shahid Beheshti University
- **Member of the Mobile Development Group,** Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, Shahid Beheshti University